<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Proven Style]]></title>
  <link href="http://provenstyle.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://provenstyle.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-08-20T10:10:03-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://provenstyle.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Michael Dudley]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registering ASP.NET in IIS]]></title>
    <link href="http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/08/19/registering-asp-dot-net/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-19T16:32:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/08/19/registering-asp-dot-net</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Every time I have set up a new development environment in the last three years I have forgotten to register Asp.net with IIS.  When I was first learning it would derail me for a quite a while.  I have done it so many times now that I recognize what is going on when I see the errors, but it is still irritating.  What was that command again?  I am putting it here so I never have to Google it again!</p>

<pre><code>aspnet_regiis
</code></pre>

<p>&ldquo;Not a recognized command!&rdquo; you say?
Yes, you have to change directories into the .net version that you are using.</p>

<pre><code>cd C:\Windows\Microsoft.NET\Framework\v4.0.30319
</code></pre>

<p>Now run the command.</p>

<p>What? That didn&rsquo;t do it either?  Don&rsquo;t forget to add the install flag.</p>

<pre><code>aspnet_regiis -i
</code></pre>

<p>Still not working?  Don&rsquo;t forget to start your command prompt as admin, and yes now you have to cd directories all over again into your .net version.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Permissions For Your App Pool]]></title>
    <link href="http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/07/31/setting-permissions-for-your-app-pool/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-31T08:37:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/07/31/setting-permissions-for-your-app-pool</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How the heck do you reference an IIS application pool user when you need to give it access to a directory?  I never can remember either! I flounder around trying different combinations.  I question whether it needs quotes.  I look for the right stack overflow question and never seem to find it.  So here it is for you and I to remember.  Don&rsquo;t worry about the spaces and no need for quotation marks.</p>

<pre><code>IIS AppPool\application pool name
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Clean]]></title>
    <link href="http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/07/13/git-clean/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-13T13:48:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://provenstyle.github.io/blog/2013/07/13/git-clean</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I love finding new commands for git that make my life simpler.  I added a new git command to my tool belt today.</p>

<pre><code>git clean -d -f
</code></pre>

<p>git clean removes files and directories that are not being tracked by git.  It is really useful for deleting the Visual Studio artifacts that hang around even if they are not being used.  It is amazing how may problems can be solved with your solution just by deleting the bin folder and recreating it.  I find this especially true when I do sweeping refactorings in my solution.</p>

<p>-n Will do a dry run. It doesn&rsquo;t remove anything it just tells you what it would delete.</p>

<p>-d Tells git to remove directories</p>

<p>-f Forces the delete</p>

<p>To delete files only and not the directories</p>

<pre><code>git clean -f
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
